[
    {
        "question" : "1.) When was the Angular Framework first introduced?", 
        "ans1" : "September 2016", 
        "ans2" : "September 2017", 
        "ans3" : "August 2015", 
        "ans4" : "December 2016", 
        "correctAns" : "September 2016"
    },
    {
        "question" : "2.) When is attendance taken during the afternoon of this ILP program?", 
        "ans1" : "5:00 PM", 
        "ans2" : "2:00 PM", 
        "ans3" : "1:00 PM", 
        "ans4" : "4:30 PM", 
        "correctAns" : "2:00 PM"
    },
    {
        "question" : "3.) The Mexican Beer Corona is what type of beer?", 
        "ans1" : "India Pale Ale", 
        "ans2" : "Baltic Porter", 
        "ans3" : "Pilfsner", 
        "ans4" : "Pale Lager", 
        "correctAns" : "Pale Lager"
    },
    {
        "question" : "4.) Before 2016, in which other year did Donald Trump run for President?", 
        "ans1" : "1988", 
        "ans2" : "2012", 
        "ans3" : "2000", 
        "ans4" : "2008", 
        "correctAns" : "2000"
    },
    {
        "question" : "5.) Which former Star Trek actor directed Three Men and a Baby (1987)?", 
        "ans1" : "Leonard Nimoy", 
        "ans2" : "William Shatner", 
        "ans3" : "George Takei", 
        "ans4" : "James Doohan", 
        "correctAns" : "Leonard Nimoy"
    },
    {
        "question" : "6.) Who had a 1983 hit with the song Africa?", 
        "ans1" : "Foreigner", 
        "ans2" : "Journey", 
        "ans3" : "Toto", 
        "ans4" : "Jim Croce", 
        "correctAns" : "Toto"
    },
    {
        "question" : "7.) How much did the indie game Cave Story cost when it was first released in 2004?", 
        "ans1" : "$0 USD", 
        "ans2" : "$5 USD", 
        "ans3" : "$10 USD", 
        "ans4" : "$15 USD", 
        "correctAns" : "$0 USD"
    },
    {
        "question" : "8.) What is the largest living organism currently known to man?", 
        "ans1" : "Blue Whale", 
        "ans2" : "Honey Fungus", 
        "ans3" : "Redwood Tree", 
        "ans4" : "Elephant", 
        "correctAns" : "Honey Fungus"
    },
    {
        "question" : "9.) Who is the current lead singer for the band Queen?", 
        "ans1" : "Freddie Mercury", 
        "ans2" : "Brian May", 
        "ans3" : "Brendon Urie", 
        "ans4" : "Adam Lambert", 
        "correctAns" : "Adam Lambert"
    },
    {
        "question" : "10.) What is the title of the latest album produced by the band Gorillaz?", 
        "ans1" : "Demon Days", 
        "ans2" : "The Now Now", 
        "ans3" : "Song Machine, Season One: Strange Timez", 
        "ans4" : "Plastic Beach", 
        "correctAns" : "Song Machine, Season One: Strange Timez"
    }
]